You've learned a lot about web development so far. I want you to take a moment to write down your thoughts about web development here. Answer the following questions:
  * What new skills have you learned?
  * What has been easy?
  * What has been difficult?
  * How have you used the problem solving strategies from the first project to overcome challenges so far?

---

Your response goes here!

除了一些基本的标签使用之外，我还学到了hr标签以及sup标签，复习了a标签以及del标签。
总体来说比较简单，难的是hr标签，一开始想用br的，但是发现没有横线，通过在MDN上进行搜索找到了hr标签。
